If technology is what
you're talking about,
We still don't trust you.
But I want to leave this place.
Don't you guys want to establish a signal?
Noberto, I know that
the safety of your team
and of Sophie is important.
Let me tell you this.
Please bring Angelito and Mikoy home.
We have to bring them back safely
for Tess's sake.
Have hope.
Thank you.
Thank you for not leaving me.
Even though I'm so weak.
It's nothing.
Don't leave me, please!
It doesn't matter who… stay by my side.
Sianong!
Will you still forgive me?
Come on!
Why now of all times?
Why now?!
I'll be on guard here.
Chiara.
I know.
Not only did I fail to get the bomb,
we also couldn't catch up
with Sofie and Angelito,
and now we're in the middle of nowhere,
while Sianong is fighting for his life.
What a series
of unfortunate events, right?
And the worst part is,
we're running out of time.
There's nothing we can do.
Angelito, not now.
Is this the end for me?
Focus, Sofie.
You can do this, Sofie.
You can do this.
Come on, Angelito.
Here.
There are tracks.
They're still here.
They couldn't have gone far.
There's a house.
Come on.
Let's check it out.
Chiara.
You're not pathetic, okay?
You've done everything you can.
Chiara.
You're already doing more than enough.
You're not alone, okay?
Always remember that,
and remember what I told you.
When the pressure gets too heavy,
we can make it lighter,
just share the burden.
Right?
I'm frustrated too, Chiara,
but we can't give up.
For the people we love, right?
And we'll never, ever
give up on each other.
Anyone home?
Open up unless you want
someone to get hurt.
Why does anyone have to get hurt?
What do you need?
Wait a minute. What are you doing here?
We're just looking for someone.
Who are you looking for?
What do you need?
Oh my.
It's Lady Amor.
Tonight may feel long,
but I'm sure
tomorrow will bring the light.
Everything will be all right.
I'll always be here for you.
No matter what happens.
And remember what I told you.
In the darkness,
the stars shine the brightest.
What are you doing here?
Everyone else has already left.
Why are you still here?
Why would I leave?
I live here. This is my home.
So you'll be the only one left
on the island?
Lord, we both know
I'm not exactly a religious girly,
but I know You can hear me.
The people here will come back.
This is where we were born and raised.
This is where we learned how to survive.
Whatever disaster comes our way,
we always find a way
to get back on our feet.
Angelito.
Is your guardian angel asleep too?
Let's go.
We're getting nowhere here.
Let's move.
Since we can't control
the variables out there,
it's best to come overprepared.
So, Team 1, Kian, you'll lead
the front line, so we can get in.
And Team 3, Dara and I.
We'll look for Mikoy, Chiara, and Sianong.
Mario, you and Ben
will secure the safe house.
Let's make sure it's on high alert.
So far, these are the top locations
where they could be.
If we have to search
every inch of this island, we will.
There it is.
We've got a signal!
Angelito.
Wake up.
That was fast!
Prayer answered right away.
Sofie is calling.
Do you ever regret it?
Regret what?
This life.
It's dangerous, chaotic,
and complicated,
all because you chose Chiara.
You know,
no matter who we choose
to spend our lives with,
we all go through hardships.
This just happens to be mine.
Ours, mine and Chiara's.
That's all.
You have a point, brother.
But don't you ever wonder
if everything you and Chiara
have fought for is worth it?
Everything you're fighting for.
But don't you ever ask yourself
what all this is?
Is it really worth it?
I'm on my way.
To answer your question, yes, of course!
It's really worth it, right?
It's all worth it.
You know,
we haven't yet seen the end of the tunnel.
But isn't it true what they say,
there's light at the end?
Also, they say,
"There's always a rainbow after the rain."
Yes, right?
There is.
But that's not how I know La Fornarina.
I really don't see her in that way.
That's not how I know Chiara.
What I know about Chiara,
there's always an agenda.
Should be a mission accomplished.
And once she has done that,
she leaves everything behind.
And if it's a lot, sorry.
It can't be!
Perhaps it was before,
when we didn't know each other.
But now,
not anymore.
My sweetheart is different.
My goodness!
I mean, love really does wonders.
You know, me and Chiara,
the meaning of mission accomplished
is clear with us,
once our dream lives are within reach.
That's all there is.
What?
You'll leave us behind?
Like what you did in Hong Kong.
You'll create new fake passports.
No, we don't have anymore secrets, right?
As long as it's just simple,
being happy, us two being together.
That's what mission accomplished
means to us.
And sooner or later,
We'll be close to reaching that.
That's it!
Now I know why
you're so in love with Chiara.
You know, it's so nice
to be witnessing this.
I mean, even her priorities have shifted.
I understand now that your love…
is important for her too.
Hopefully I get to witness
your mission accomplished.
Once you achieve the simple life.
Thanks.
Angelito hasn't been responsive
for a long while now.
Will he wake up?
I'm doing everything I can, Sophie.
Just have faith.
Agents, stay alert.
You all know what to do.
Alex! Dara!
Rafa!
That's all you've got?!
Good. Let's move faster!
There!
Hey!
That was a gunshot.
My gun too!
Could that be Agent Alex?
Maybe rescue is here.
Or maybe it's La Morte Bianca.
She sent reinforcements to finish us off.
What's important is we're ready, okay?
How's your wound?
It's just a graze, ma'am.
Who is it?
There's more.
-Hold your fire! It's us.
-It's them!
Wait.
Sianong?
Sianong!
Duh!
Angelito, wake up!
Help!
All these lives are on the line
because of me.
But that's the truth, sir.
If I'd just listened,
all this wouldn't have happened.